Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
- United Textile Workers. Local 1603, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 51: Edwards returns from Passaic, by Laurence Todd, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 52: Passaic strikers answer Davis, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 53: Coolidge rebuffs Passaic strikers, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 54: Passaic strikers heard in Washington, by Laurence Todd, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 55: Police won't arrest others who beat strikers, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 56: Police club strikers, reporters - smash cameras, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 57: Passaic strikers join old AF of L unions in great parade, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 58: Shows Passaic textile profits high, by Laurence Todd, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 59: Another 'outside influence' enters Passaic, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 60: Green explains textile stand, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 61: Passaic children picket Coolidge, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 62: Passaic issue will not down, by Laurence Todd, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - Item 63: Coolidge will not protect citizens, by Laurence Todd, Publication (Box 389, Folder 3)
- United Textile Workers of America. Department of Research and Education, Publication (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Textile strike of 1926: Passaic, Clifton, Garfield, Lodi, New Jersey., Publication (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Officer's and shop steward's manual, Publication (Box 389, Folder 4)
    Author: United Textile Workers of America. Dept. of Research and Education
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America)., Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bulletin IV, Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
    Author: Textile Workers Organizing Committee
  - Item 2: American Arbitration Association, Administrator - Voluntary labor arbitration tribunal, Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: In the matter of the arbitration between Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company and Textile Workers Union of America, CIO Local 2188, Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: American Arbitration Association, Administrator - Voluntary Labor Arbitration Tribunal -- In the matter of the arbitration between Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, Local 2188 and Bigelow- Sanford Carpet Company, Inc., Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Fall River Textile Man. Assoc.; New Bedford Cotton Manufacturers' Assoc and Textile Workers' Union of America, 1949; Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
    Author: New Bedford Cotton Manufacturers' Association
  - Item 6: New wage levels and fringe issues, by Solomon Barkin, 1947; Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Sixth Annual Management Conference -- Statement on Foreign Trade Policy, 1954; Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
    Author: Solomon Barkin
  - Item 8: Songs, Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: What do your dues do?, Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Area redevelopment clear the way for new jobs and new growth, Publication (Box 390, Folder 1)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America)., Publication (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Toward fairer federal labor standards, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The application of quality control techniques in determining work assignments and standards, 1954; Publication (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Wage increases do not mean price increases, 1945; Publication (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Trade union approach to wage incentive plans (reproduced from Time and Motion Study), 1953; Publication (Box 390, Folder 2)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Rules for union meetings, 1943; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
    Author: TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America). Educational Dept.
    Notes: Second copy. Second edition.
  - Item 2: So you're a steward!: a handbook for TWUA shop stewards and department committees, 1943; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: So you're a steward!: a handbook for TWUA shop stewards and department committees, 1946; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
    Notes: Second edition.
  - Item 4: TWUA, how it works--: the operation of your union, the Textile Workers Union of America, CIO., 1945; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: TWUA: it's your union., 1944; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Manual of instruction for TWUA shop stewards in the mills of the American Woolen Company., 1946; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Toward a new day, 1943; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Your pension plan: National plan of textile workers pension fund, 1973; Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Your pension plan: TWUA Pension Fund, Publication (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: The TWUA Welfare Plan: its organization and operation, 1960-1969 (Box 390, Folder 3)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: So you're a steward!: a handbook for TWUA shop stewards and department committees, 1946; Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
    Notes: Second edition. Second copy
  - Item 2: Manual of instruction for TWUA shop stewards in the mills of the American Woolen Company., 1946; Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: So you're a steward!: a handbook for TWUA shop stewards and department committees, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
    Notes: Third edition
  - Item 4: Your union: a story with pictures., 1944; Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Where your international unio dollar goes, 1946; Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: TWUA Educational activities - (excerpts dealing with education, from the Exec. Council Report, 1946; Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Educational program of the Textile Workers Union of America, 1946; Publication (Box 390, Folder 4)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Building a textile union., 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Free enterprise for whom?, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
    Author: Emil Rieve
  - Item 3: Topical outlines for labor history, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Quotations and readings in labor history - for use with TWUA Labor History outline, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Instructor's outline for parliamentary procedure, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Instructor's outline for collective bargaining, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Instructors' outline on 'effective speaking': a guide for those handling TWUA groups, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Instructors outline on labor history, 1948; Publication (Box 390, Folder 5)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 391, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: TWUA Film Catalogue, 1949; Publication (Box 391, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Note to instructor, 1949; Publication (Box 391, Folder 1)
    Author: TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America). Education Dept.
  - Item 3: Outline of union, Publication (Box 391, Folder 1)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: TWUA songs, 1950; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
    Notes: Fourth edition
  - Item 2: The How, why, who of TWUA., 1951; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: 20 questions and answers for TWUA stewards, 1950; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
    Notes: First edition
  - Item 4: Something new in union education, 1950; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: What to do with retired members, Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Officers guide to effective union meetings, 1950; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Teaching guide for TWUA Stewards, 1951; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Education Newsletter - May 14, 1969, Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: advertisement - When you join The Progressive Union, 1950; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: TWUA Summer Institutes Training for Leadership, 1950; Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: What your TWUA-CIO dollar buys for you, Publication (Box 391, Folder 2)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: What to do about non-members, 1955; Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: TWUA songs, 1956; Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
    Notes: Sixth edition
  - Item 3: Rules for union meetings, 1955; Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
    Notes: Second edition
  - Item 4: 20 questions and answers for TWUA stewards, 1957; Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Correspondence Course questionnaire, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Basic unionism a TWUA correspondence course, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The American Federation of Teachers - Summer Workshop for Eastern United States, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Correspondence Course -- Lessons I-VI, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: What is the steward?, 1956; Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: TWUA Education Institute courses, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Getting good stewards, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Pointers for TWUA discussion leaders, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Contract content, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Grievance problems, Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: El Manual del Delegado: 20 Preguntas y respuestas, 1955; Publication (Box 391, Folder 3)
    Author: Instituto de Relaciones del Trabajo
    Language: Spanish.
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 20 questions and answers for TWUA stewards, 1963; Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: When you've got a grievance, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Okay, let's talk about stirkes, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: How the union works, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Rx for an ailing industry, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Ten points for meetings, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Trade-union attitudes and their effect upon productivity, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Your library can serve your union, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Testimony of Solomon Barkin, 1960; Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: TWUA activity evaluation form, 1963; Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Education Newsletter - Sept. 12, 1969, Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Tips on running a successful Union Affair - 25th Anniversary Celebration, 1963; Publication (Box 391, Folder 4)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Almost unbelievable ... the story of an industry, a union and law, 1961; Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Half a million forgotten people, 1944; Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The TWUA story: they said it couldn't be done, 1964; Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: They said it couldn't be done: a history of the Textile Workers Union of America, 1965; Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: They said it couldn't be done: a history of the Textile Workers Union of America, 1965; Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: An outline of TWUA, AFL-CIO History, 1960; Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: A case study: Union - busting in the South, 1971; Publication (Box 392, Folder 1)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Stewards handbook: Textile Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: College Education Financing - TWUA Members' guide, Publication (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The Newsletter -, Publication (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Education Newsletter - Dec. 1969, Aug, 1969, Oct. 1969, Nov. 1969, Publication (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Manual of instruction for TWUA shop stewards in the plants of the American Viscose Corporation., Publication (Box 392, Folder 2)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Infamous Failure, Publication (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Financial Report, Textile Workers Union of America, 1947-1948 (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Financial Report, Textile Workers Union of America, 1954-1964 (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Audited Financial Report - 1948-1952 (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Textile Economic Policy: Study in irresponsibility (reprinted from the Exec. Council Report), 1952; Publication (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The new social security act: TWUA guide for shop stewards, Publication (Box 392, Folder 3)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 392, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: TWUA: Social Security manual: a guide to the new 1950 Social Security Act, Publication (Box 392, Folder 4)
    Author: TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America). Insurance and Health Dept.
- Greater New York Joint Board, TWUA, Publication (Box 392, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Joint Board News - v.IV, no. 1-2; v.III, no. 1-3, 5-10; v.I, no. 1-2, 1944-1947 (Box 392, Folder 5)
    Author: Greater New York Joint Board, TWUA
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Philadelphia story: how the TWUA-CIO Philadelphia Joint Board works for you, 1944; Publication (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Your union: who, what, why, where, how, Publication (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Joint Boards, 1941-1948 (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Strike Bulletin - no. 6, 1951; Publication (Box 392, Folder 6)
    Author: Pittsylvania County Joint Board, TWUA
  - Item 5: The History of the Ladis Auxiliary of Biddeford-Saco Joint Board, 1952; Publication (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Fall Rivera brighter to-morrow, Publication (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Progress through unity -, Publication (Box 392, Folder 6)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Statement of Textile Workers Union of America presented to Senate Committee on Labor, 1947; Publication (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Taft-Hartleyism in textiles, 1953; Publication (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: NLRB ground rules for organizing campaigns, 1956; Publication (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Analysis of the Taft-Ives-Hartley Act - prepared by TWUA Legal Dept., 1947; Publication (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The Matt Lynch Story, Publication (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The Story of Matt Lynch: an example of service, Publication (Box 392, Folder 7)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Taft-Hartleyism in southern textiles, feudalism with a new face; statement before Subcommittee on Labor and Public Welfare, United States Senate, prepared October 9, 1950., Publication (Box 393, Folder 1)
    Author: Isadore Katz
  - Item 2: This industrial giant is fighting you! (article), 1952; Publication (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: International labor standards, a key to world security, 1945; Publication (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Employer material used in TWUA-CIO Organizing Campaigns, 1950; Publication (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Behind Taft-Hartley's mumbo-jumbo, Publication (Box 393, Folder 1)
    Author: Irving Kahan
  - Item 6: Danger: watch out!: what you should know about the Taft-Hartley Law, 1947; Publication (Box 393, Folder 1)
    Author: United Textile Workers of America. Research Dept.
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Behind Taft-Hartley's mumbo-jumbo, Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: 1951 TWUA - Legislative-Pac Institute - conference schedule, Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Textile labor - minimum wageup, up, up, Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Please don't buy Lowentstein Products, Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Textile union workers study bargaining at Wellesley Parley, 1949; Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: News from Textile Workers Union of America, 1954; Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: TWUA, how it works--: the operation of your union, the Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1945; Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The joint safety program of the Forstmann Woolen Company and Local 656, Textile Workers Union of Americam CIO, 1948; Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
    Author: Rutgers University. Institute of Management and Labor Relations
  - Item 9: Your union dollar goes to work, Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: TWUA-CIO where your international union dollar goes, Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: We're glad to see you, Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: The fight against substandards: facts on the cotton wage case before the National War Labor Board., 1945; Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Tell the world: TWUA publicity manual, 1947; Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
    Author: E. M. Schoffstall
  - Item 14: Ten years of southern progress: the story of Local 549, Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, Lynchburg, Va., Publication (Box 393, Folder 2)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 393, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor songs, 1939; Publication (Box 393, Folder 3)
    Author: Zilphia Horton
  - Item 2: All rights denied, 1955; Publication (Box 393, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Substandard conditions of living, 1944; Publication (Box 393, Folder 3)
    Author: TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America). Research Dept.
  - Item 4: Building a union of textile workers, 1939; Publication (Box 393, Folder 3)
    Author: Textile Workers Organizing Committee.
  - Item 5: We're glad to see you, Publication (Box 393, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Unions and grievances (reprinted from Personnel Journal, June, 1943), Publication (Box 393, Folder 3)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Staff manual, (looseleaf binder with various handouts), 1959; Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Chins up: is still the word in Henderson, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Hold the line in Henderson!, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
    Notes: Poster. 2 copies
  - Item 4: We need teachers so we train them, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Economic policies for a leader of the free world, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: article - Saved by the union, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: How to check the books: a manual for TWUA Auditing Committees, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Principles for area redevelopment legislation (reprinted from the August, 1959 issue of Labor Law Journal, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: All rights denied, 1955; Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Two views of Henderson, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: How the union works, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Henderson: its your fight too!, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Why workers organize: the rights reasons results of unions, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Get this on your product and help everybody, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: TWUA volunteer organizing program, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Carolina Textile Workers seek modern housing: a report on new housing needs in Erwin, North Carolina, Publication (Box 393, Folder 4)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Biography of William Pollock, General President, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Statement of Boyd E. PaytonNov. 3, 1960, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
    Author: Boyd E. Payton
  - Item 3: Kays GaryWentworth..your street?...Nov. 3, 1960, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Kays GaryWrite hero of Henderson care of Martinsville JailApr. 15, 1961, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The News and Observer, Raleigh, NCA tuge at the Conscience by Charles ClayNov. 23, 1960, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
    Author: Charles Clay
  - Item 6: News fromfor release - P.M.'s Thursday, Nov. 3, 1960 -- Here to bid farewell to eight Henderson strike leaders who will begin serving two to 10 year sentences., Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Textile Labor / Official Publication of the Textile Workers Union of America, 1962; Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.23:no.4. 2 copies
  - Item 8: Correspondence - Dear Rev. Webber - Recently I returned from one of several visits to Henderson, NC deeply troubled, 1960; Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
    Author: Press Associates
  - Item 9: The hollow promise: the conspiracy to deny Southern textile workers the benefits of collective bargaining., 1967; Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Almost unbelievable ... the story of an industry, a union and law., 1961; Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Almost unbelievable ...: the story of an industry, a union and law: a sumpplemental report, 1961; Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Henderson: it's your fight, too!, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: America's stake in the South, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Run a good union meeting, Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: This is the Textile Workers Union of America., Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Union fratricide: the textile workers split, 1964; Publication (Box 394, Folder 1)
    Author: Frank Traver De Vyver
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Textile Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
    Notes: Poster/Flyer
  - Item 2: JP Stevens faces jail, Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Protect your future!, Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: President Woodrow Wilson, Textile Workers Union of America, the Union with Grievance know-how, Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: TWUA keeps pace with a changing world, Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Ten years of law violations by JP Stevens & Co., Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: It's your right to join the Union, Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The story of a strike, 1955; Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Conspiracy in Southern textiles, 1967; Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: This is the real J.P. Stevens: the Textile Workers Union of America tells the story of a textile giant., 1975; Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Third party: red ally of reaction: an analysis, 1948; Publication (Box 394, Folder 2)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: How the union works, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Union's role in job safety act enforcement, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: More than wages, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Your union has done a big job, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: A bill of rights for Southern Textile Workers, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Ups & downs of the Textile Industry, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Toward a new day, 1943; Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Strikes vs. the Common Cold, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The cost of living has gone up!, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: List of secretaries and addresses, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Barriers to communication between men by FJ Roethlisberger, Publication (Box 394, Folder 3)
    Author: F. J. Roethlisberger
- United Textile Workers of America, Publication (Box 394, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Date set for National Labor Relations Board Election!, 1944; Publication (Box 394, Folder 4)